Alex Fallaw

Graphic Designer & Web Developer

I'm a graphic design and computer science student at the University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign. I've been passionate about art for almost a decade, experimenting with several different art forms over the years. I have also come to love coding, both web design and program development. I really enjoy the problem-solving involved in programming, and I appreciate the flexibility it gives me in manifesting my designs. I'm looking for an internship or entry-level job in web or graphic design.

Skill Highlights

Digital design WordPress

Instructional graphic design HTML
Website design CSS

Wireframing Java
Collaborative story writing JavaScript

Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, React JS

Illustrator, InDesign) Git

Figma SketchBook

Education

University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign Graphic Design, BFA with minor in Computer Science 2022-present

University of Wisconsin Eau Claire Graphic Communications 2021-2022

Parkland College General Studies 2020-2021

Work Experience

Lowes Cashier

Responsibilities:

Deliver excellent customer service at the register

Answer customer questions

Was awarded a service award for customer service

May 2021 - August 2021

Champaign, IL

House Cleaner

Responsibilities:

Dishes

Vacuuming

General cleaning

December 2019 - August 2021

Champaign, IL